teachingbd24.com 2019-03-30

# Privacy Policy | Teaching BD

## Analytics

  * Google Analytics  
Personal Data: Cookie and Usage Data  
Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google. Google utilizes the data collected to track and examine the use of www.example.com, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.  
Google may use the data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.Personal data collected: Cookie and Usage Data. Place of processing: USA. Find Google’s [privacy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)[ policy here](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).
  * You can opt out by clicking [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)

## Adsense

  * Google AdSense is an advertising service provided by Google. **[teachingbd24.com](https://teachingbd24.com/)**  uses the “Doubleclick” Cookie, which tracks the use of **[teachingbd24.com](https://teachingbd24.com/)**  and user behavior concerning ads, products and the services we offer.  
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data. Place of processing: USA. You can find the AdSense [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/) here.
  * You may decide to disable all the Doubleclick Cookies by clicking on: [google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout?hl=en](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/html/blocked-cookies.html).

## What do we do with your data?

The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Application to provide its services, as well as for the following purposes: Analytics and Interaction with external social networks and platforms. By any mean, we don’t use your data for any other purposes.

_**We don’t sell your data, or modify it or use it by any other means.**_

### Privacy

**[teachingbd24.com](https://teachingbd24.com/) respects your privacy.**

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of **[teachingbd24.com](https://teachingbd24.com/)**.

**Credit card details**

**[teachingbd24.com](https://teachingbd24.com/)**  will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on **[teachingbd24.com](https://teachingbd24.com/)**.

**External Sites.**

**[teachingbd24.com](https://teachingbd24.com/)**  is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

**Cookies**

A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows **[teachingbd24.com](https://teachingbd24.com/)**  to recognize you each time you visit this site(customisation etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and **[teachingbd24.com](https://teachingbd24.com/)**  does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.

**Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet**

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to **[teachingbd24.com](https://teachingbd24.com/)**  and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through **[teachingbd24.com](https://teachingbd24.com/)**  have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

For any other information email webmaster
